Are you awake?
Wh-Who are you?
I'm a doctor from Chiba.
My name is Date.
A doctor?
It's only a quick fix,
but with some rest, the bleeding should stop.
R-Really?
I thought I was done for...
I thought I'd never see my wife and son again.
Date-sensei, thank you!
Thank you!
It's my duty as a doctor.
Now, stay here and rest.
Thank you so much...
Fool.
I saved you, so I'd be able to use you later.
Why the hell did I have to be
dragged back here, anyway?
To hell with this!
Wh-Who are you?!
S-Sakamoto-han, you came back?
Of course I did.
What are you doing here?
Get away from him!
So he had friends with him?
N-No...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I just happened to be passing by.
I saw he was hurt, so I treated him.
I'm a doctor...
Saving lives is my job.
I've no intention of taking part
in this barbaric game!
A doctor?
S-Sakamoto-han,
he saved my life.
He's a good man.
You can trust him.
Nice work, cripple.
It looks professionally done.
Maybe he really is a doctor.
O-Oh...
Stupid teenage girl.
What do you know?
I'm sorry.
I was just surprised.
No, as long as we're clear, it's fine.
I understand completely.
One thing, though...
Show me your BIMs, would you?
That will tell me whether you're
playing the game or not.
Of course.
I've never seen this type on the island.
Remote controlled.
You flip the switch on the BIM,
and then use this remote control to activate it.
They're used for traps.
I used to fall for those all the time!
Because you just rush forward.
Anyone who gets hit with traps
isn't paying enough attention.
What does that mean?
If you ask me, people who are
good with traps are just jerks.
What? These guys are gamers?
They're just wasting their lives.
U-Um...
There isn't any sign you've ever used your BIMs.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Not at all.
I was lucky I didn't run into
anyone else for three days.
If you don't mind...
Would you help us try to escape this island?
Escape the island?
Yes.
We'll get eight chips, call in the helicopter,
and then steal it and run.
I see...
Come on, you don't really expect
it to be that easy, do you?
We have three chips.
Three?!
You already have three?
Yes.
P-Please allow me to help...
We'll all survive together.
Thank you.
Date Masahito.
Sakamoto Ryouta.
This is Himiko.
The one you treated is Taira-san.
Nice to meet you.
He was abandoned here
because someone hated him...
A carrier!
They're going to drop supplies again?
Sakamoto-kun, let's go get them.
If we all work together, we'll have
better odds of getting them.
That's true.
Taira-san, we're going to get food.
Y-You're leaving again?
Don't worry.
We'll come back with some delicious food.
Look forward to it.
The three of them together equal six chips.
The Strongest Player
Fortune is smiling on me.
One's landing nearby.
The wind's strong.
It's blowing away!
It'll land in the sea...
Don't give up.
We have to get it.
A radar.
Someone else is after the food.
There are six of them.
What do we do?
Turn back?
We don't need to turn back.
If we just show them we're
getting it, no matter what,
we can scare them off.
Everyone's watching each other.
Two are getting closer.
Two gave up and left.
Two appear to be just watching.
This is bad.
It's heading toward the two
who are getting close...
We have to show them our intent.
That we won't give up!
We're just about to reach it.
What?
He isn't backing off?
It's risky to use BIMs here.
The first to leave the forest
will be an easy target.
But if I'm too slow, he'll take it!
Damn it!
He isn't
backing off, not even a little?
What's he thinking?
Wait.
Those sunglasses...
I've seen him before!
Ryouta!
Oda!
You die, too.
Where is he?
Okay, got it...
Damn it.
What's wrong?
I can't get the parachute off.
A burning gas type!
The wind will spread the gas.
Date-san!
Run!
Forget the trunk...
Get away from that smoke!
I'll leave the food to you, Sakamoto.
There it is, Sakamoto-kun.
Take it!
Wha—
That was close...
Nice, Sakamoto-kun!
Run!
Don't let him get the trunk!
Of course not.
After all this, I won't let him take it!
I did well to kill her,
but I don't want to go get her chip...
It's gross.
Whatever.
When Oda gets back, I'll make
him grab the chip and BIMs...
What?
You're alive?
Too bad.
I panicked and tossed that BIM away.
I should have thrown it back at you.
You only have timer BIMs, don't you?
So what?
Mine are crackers.
Head-to-head, I have the advantage.
But at this range, neither of us will
make it out unscathed if we use BIMs.
I've got this.
So what?
You won't let me get away?
You and your stupid stun gun...
I've seen your type before,
ugly girls who carry all kinds of
ridiculous crap for "self-defense."
Did you expect me to run after seeing that?
Come on, then.
I'll beat the crap out of you...
Damn it.
This fire...
A flame type?
Another enemy?
Damn, I'm totally surrounded!
He can't escape now.
We'll just watch him burn to ash.
No, you have to finish him.
Shut up!
No one asked your opinion, kid.
Shut up, and watch!
But this isn't good...
I'm taking this.
You've gotta be kidding.
That bastard!
Isn't there a beach up that way?
What of it?
That's probably where they'll try to come up.
I-I know that!
You don't have to tell me.
I'm going.
Don't get in my way.
No, I won't get in your way.
I'm sick of stupid adults.
What? You're shaking.
You're scared, aren't you?
I guess you must be,
if you need to carry that thing.
I bet you're a neat freak, right?
Had a bad experience before
you lost your virginity?
Shut up! That's not true!
The way you're shouting makes me doubt that...
Could I be right?
You're carrying that around
because you can't trust anyone?
It's proof that you have a weak heart.
No.
That's not true!
You're a stupid brat...
Maybe I'll strangle you right here.
Wh-Who is this woman?
She isn't normal...
Your stun gun can't help you now.
A strong body is the important thing.
You're tougher than you look.
Just give in already...
That's right.
Why am I trying to survive?
I tried to die so many times.
Why?
N-No...
That isn't why!
I don't feel that way about him at all.
That's impossible.
But right now, I don't want to die!
Stop struggling already...
I won't give up!
I want to stay with you.
It's not like that!
How dare you, you ugly bitch?!
Enough of your shit!
That hurt...
What the hell was that for?!
Still standing?
The voltage is dropping!
How dare you!
Come on and die, already!
Wh-What is this?!
Who is that?
Is he with that girl?
She's still alive?
Are you okay?
That was close...
Are you hurt?
I-I'm okay.
That almost killed me, too.
Good...
I'm glad you weren't badly hurt.
If I hadn't come by, it could've been bad.
Wh-What is he talking about?
He tried to kill us both.
But he's talking like he saved me.
I can't trust him at all.
But if I say that out loud,
he might kill me now.
Thank you for saving me...
Can you walk?
Let's go look for Sakamoto-kun.
R-Right.
Enemies are everywhere.
The only person I can trust is Ryouta...
Ryouta, please...
Don't die!
Where is he?
Did he run away?
No, he's good.
He's waiting to ambush me somewhere.
It isn't him.
Is he the one who used those flame types?
Hey, there's no one here...
That kid was full of crap.
Wh-What's that doing there?
One of them must've hidden it there
so that the other wouldn't take it.
Idiots.
They were so focused on each other
that, in the end,
they let me walk off with it.
Don't move!
Move an inch, and I'll shove
this cracker up your ass.
Drop all your BIMs...
And the trunk, and your chips!
Now put your hands on your head.
He's being too obedient.
I give up.
I surrender.
Come over and get them.
Are you scared?
Then do you want me to move away?
Do it.
Slowly.
Why isn't he more worried?
He killed without hesitation
for those BIMs and chips.
And now he's just giving them up?
This doesn't make sense.
Something is wrong.
But what?
A booby trap?
No, all his BIMs are there.
He didn't have time to place anything.
Could he have a remote control type?
That must be it...
He set this trap,
a remote controlled BIM, a long time ago.
In other words, that trunk
is surrounded by mines.
Show me your hands.
Turn your palms toward me!
Why?
Just do it...
Now!
Fine, fine.
What?!
He must have them...
Am I overthinking this?
Is there some other way?
But what?
Is he buying time while he
waits for his buddies to come?
That would mean it's dangerous to delay.
I'll have to take a chance...
You fell for it.
Die.
What?
I-It can't be Ryouta...
I won.
What?!
Pretty smart.
However,
I won't lose at BTOOOM!.
The first one to move wins.
Stay on the defensive,
and you'll lose your chance.
Ryouta,
that is the only difference between us...
Whether or not you can understand this.
Episode 10: High Level